I am getting a lot of challans from you, I will
also take my interest, Sonth, I was with the motor
family, how did you guys come, no problem, everyone must be
very nice and friend, sorry friend, the
blocks were not coming for a long time, so
why were the blocks not coming, you will know the result
at the end of this video and today you
people must be thinking that why is R Bergman monk
not at his address, so for a long time the
oil change indicator was on on it, for
four-five days I had to get it serviced
and was
not able to submit its insurance because I was
not feeling well, if you
subscribe then you will know in this video that
if you
subscribe to the scooter and
how much its posting video of ours on it, the
service center is about half an hour away from here, but how much time will it take you, you can
try the 10-15 second remedy, do it, it has
come to our notice yesterday morning, we have
Suzuki showrooms at many places
and its service center is next to it,
do it,
158 was thankfully, that is Manidra good Mandawar
Samrau is the numerical strength which is the wound
in the Amazon jungle, it is stronger than a window
or without the installation of a pimple,
so subscribe to this side of
crazy that then the new
laughing
number from Chittor to Saudi Arabia that when one Udaipur
[Music]
Ajay [Music] do it
[Music] do it
that
Shahrukh could have
extinguished it do it do it
salute to Shubh
Choghadiya
30 minutes I am not able to understand how
[Music]
so finally our scooter has been serviced
and you can see what a shine oh
man dum it is awesome after servicing and polishing that ah
where is it done do it
subscribe our service is done and
insurance is done and
I have also topped up the petrol so it does not matter if it is
costing then the service cost is
200 ₹5 and the insurance
cost of Renuka is around 800 rupees so that means 225
what is nothing for this point machine
means my Honda Activa it
subscribe
button
[Music]
subscribe like this
appointed a lot more  I mean
school means this
appointment is
good and that its braking, this
explanation headlight I have already told you all about it
in the old video if you haven't
seen it then you can go and watch it and this was
my last free service so now lactamase
will be my pet service and out of that this one
which will bring you
closer to big stories its
subscribe sure nothing has happened to me right now
including the table and engine oil I
mean it was used in the video
but I
need a
subscribe I don't know it causes a lot of
damage I am
Sohar friend I mean
what is going on after servicing friend it was running very well before
and you mean it has become amazingly smooth
and today I noticed that it has a
mark brake pedal
108 that's why it works amazingly against the country I
mean mind
blowing it just happened with me that
I was driving
subscribe and the car in front of me
suddenly hit it
I had made it so you
know that now nothing can happen to
me with my old experience I would
push it so
if you press hard then a little
and the front of it
felt that  Nothing like that, I
immediately pressed both the backs and a little CEO
means he was so happy friend, I was feeling scared
and I also agreed that this
means how is he, so
Nitin friend, I mean job friend, I mean ABS is not there
in the scooter yet, I
mean ABS but it works, the mark is towards ABS
and I don't particularly like the brakes of the driver, I do
n't like my Pulsar at all, but friend, by the way,
director ma'am, it was
fun to use the brake of the relation, it was
fun, that's why the vehicles of Mahek and Sukhi,
their braking is very
good, many companies
use it friend, a little bit of good
home PR on this occasion, if you subscribe to
Servi
Tennyson Investment, do
not think that the
money should not be wasted, right now I have got a good road
and will push it a little and
see how it should be, if it gets less
then oil and oil
and I mean you will
put your feet from the school, so
guys, I was not coming to the block for a long time, so
this is the result, so not feeling well, a
little wow, I was feeling a little low, so
I was not able to make the block so I was getting
tensed, friend I am not getting the block, I am
not afraid, I am not able to find the block, so thinking about
this thing, I started
correcting the over and started making changes, then
after that I stopped sleeping, I
mean I was silent for two-three days, I was like this, I
mean I was not able to sleep, I mean some
things happen in life which are
not in your control, but still, I was with you only for How to
Make Yourself,
Jai Ho
Om Bhai Ji,
25 minutes of Atimik, it is not like that, friend, I have
enjoyed it,
Ajay is
playing a great role, ah, do it, do it,
if you have got some information in the video, then
please
subscribe and get your friend to
subscribe too, your little
support means a lot to us, click on the idol,
I have said it before also, so like it, I will
make this video, do like, share
subscribe, my Sat Shri Akaal
salam to all of you, Namaste, live life happily, I have demanded
that Bigg Boss should
not be played with drums, turn
off the Bluetooth settings  Do it
[music]
Do it